(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-04T09:59:59.490520",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Hapi!
It's our birthday!
Are you ready?
FUWAMOCO!
白上フブキ
Shirakami Fubuki
大神ミオ
Ookami Mio
宝鐘マリン
Houshou Marine
尾丸ポルカ
Omaru Polka
博衣こより
Hakui Koyori
シオリ・ノヴェラ
Shiori Novella
古石ビジュウ
Koseki Bijou
ネリッサ・レイヴンクロフト
Nerissa Ravencroft
Hold me baby 踊ろうよSunday
Hold me baby, let's dance on Sunday
Touch me baby 気分はHoliday
Touch me baby, feeling like a Holiday
PARTY☆NIGHT It's our birthday!
イヤなこと全部
Let's forget all the bad things,
忘れちゃおっ
leaving them all behind.
一晩眠って
Sleep for a night,
目覚めたら happy girl
and when you wake up, a happy girl.
夢の途中で出逢う不思議
Meeting by chance mid-dream is mysterious,
悪夢を食べてるバクたちも good friends
and even dream-eating tapirs are good friends.
お菓子も食べてるボクたちも good friends
We who eat sweets are also good friends!
いつもならば
When we're together,
おしゃべりもしない
we don't even chat much—
窮屈な人気味なリズムで変身
Transforming from stiff people with strange rhythms!
Hold me baby ノリノリ party
Hold me baby, ongoing party,
瞳まで輝いて
to the point that my eyes shine.
Touch me baby are you ready ok?
楽しもうよ君も
Let's have a good time, and you too!
Hold me baby 踊ろうよ sunday
Hold me baby, let's dance, it's Sunday,
ステップを踏みましょう
let's take a step together.
Touch me baby 気分は holiday
Touch me baby, it feels like a holiday,
スペシャルな時間を
into this special time.
疲れすぎて
When you're overtired
臆病な日には
and feeling timid on such days,
まぶた閉じて
close your eyes
アクセスしてみて
and try accessing it—
have a PARTY NIGHT!
Hold me baby ウキウキ lady
Hold me baby, upbeat lady,
ストレスは溜めないで
don't let stress bottle up.
Touch me baby キラキラ body
Touch me baby, sparkling body,
リフレッシュしようよ
let's get refreshed!
Hold me baby 踊ろうよ sunday
Hold me baby, let's dance, it's Sunday,
心にも栄養を
nourishing your heart too.
Touch me baby 気分は holiday
Touch me baby, it feels like a holiday,
星空のメロディ
the melody of the starry sky.
Hold me baby ウキウキ lady
Hold me baby, upbeat lady,
Touch me baby キラキラ body
Touch me baby, sparkling body,
Hold me baby 踊ろうよ sunday
Hold me baby, let's dance, it's Sunday,
Touch me baby 気分は holiday
Touch me baby, it feels like a holiday,
Hold me baby ウキウキ lady
Hold me baby, upbeat lady,
ふわふわ もこもこ
Fuwa-fuwa, moko-moko!
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Demon Realm Guard Dog Sisters☆★
この世界に爆誕“BAU”DOLです
Bursting into this world as "BAU"DOLs!
BAU!! BAU!!
Fuwawa!!
Mococo!!
フワプラスモコハフワモコ
Fuwa plus moco is FUWAMOCO!
Fuwawa!!
Mococo!!
フワプラスモコハフワモコ
Fuwa plus moco is FUWAMOCO!
BAU BAU～!!
Wake upしたら君にmorning
Wake up and give you the morning,
Newな出会い鼻効かせsearchして
searching out new encounters keenly.
ドキドキDoggy
Doki-doki Doggy,
右に左Bau Bau Bau
right to left, Bau Bau Bau!
悩んでいてもきちゃうFuture
Even when worrying, the future comes along,
まずは目の前の道Stepして
so first step onto the path right before you.
Happy Lucky Puppy
一緒に歩こうよ
let's walk together!
ドーナツの穴の中にはきっときっと夢が詰まってるから
Inside the hole of a donut, surely, dreams are packed!
ふわふわ もこもこ
Fuwa-fuwa, moko-moko,
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Demon Realm Guard Dog Sisters☆★!
2匹が揃えばもう大騒ぎ
When two of us gather, it's total chaos!
もわもわ はろはろ BAUBAU!!
Mowamowa, halohalo, BAUBAU!!
迷わずにGo my way
Without hesitating, go my way,
君の絶対味方“BAU”DOLです
your absolute ally, "BAU"DOLs!
BAU!! BAU!!
Fuwawa!!
Mococo!!
フワプラスモコハフワモコ
Fuwa plus moco is FUWAMOCO!
Fuwawa!! Mococo!!
フワプラスモコハフワモコ
Fuwa plus moco is FUWAMOCO!
ひとりじゃないよWe're together
You're not alone, we're together,
Heart繋がってる君とChatして
hearts connected, chatting with you.
Fluffy Fuzzy Yappy 一緒に歌おうよ
Fluffy, fuzzy, yappy, let's sing together!
ドーナツの穴の向こうへ
Beyond the hole of the donut,
きっときっと君が待っているから
surely, surely, because you're waiting for us!
ふわふわ もこもこ
Fuwa-fuwa, moko-moko,
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Demon Realm Guard Dog Sisters☆★!
2匹が揃えばもう止まらない
When two of us gather, there's no stopping us!
お耳も尻尾もお触りは厳禁××
Ears and tails are strictly off-limits!
スリル満点爆弾“BAU”DOLです
A thrill-filled, max-points bomb "BAU"DOL!
BAU!! BAU!!
Hey!! Ruffians!!
It's our birthday, huh?
Can I got a heck yeah!?
Let's shout "BAU"!!
BAU!! BAU!!
Now, hear the howling of my soul!!
Are you ready?!
Moco-chan!! 生誕だから可愛く歌おって言ったでしょ!!
Moco-chan!! Didn't I tell you we should sing it cute since it's our birthday?!
bau bau!!
じゃあBメロから…せーの！
Then starting from the B melody... Ready, go!
ドーナッツリングに誓って
Sworn on the donut ring,
ずっと ずっと
always, always,
笑顔を守るから
I will protect your smile.
ふわふわ もこもこ
Fuwawa, Mococo,
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Underworld Guard Dog Sisters☆★
2匹が揃えばもう大騒ぎ
When the two of us get together, it's total chaos!
もがもあ ハロハロ 迷わずに Go my way
Motto, moao, hello hello, straying not, go my way.
君の絶対味方“BAU”DOLです
We are your absolute allies, "BAU"DOLs!
この世界に爆誕“BAU”DOLです
Exploding into this world as "BAU"DOLs!
Fuwawa!! Mococo!!
Fuwa+Moco は FUWAMOCO!!
Fuwa+Moco is FUWAMOCO!!
Fuwawa!! Mococo!!
Fuwa+Moco は FUWAMOCO!!
Fuwa+Moco is FUWAMOCO!!
Oh my god!
It's our first birthday live ever, ruffians!
We're a very special day!
Our Fuwamoco Birthday Party Night!
Wait, is our first birthday live ever, right? All-time... All-time birthday live!
Wait, is it our first birthday live ever, right? All-time... All-time birthday live!
Wait, just... exactly whose birthday is it, huh?
Ah... Oh! Mococo-chan, like, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
I'm not a chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa!
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo!
Together, we're FUWAMOCO! Bau bau!
And it's my birthday! It's my birthday! It's our birthday night! Bau bau!
Ah, if you're a little confused right now, that's okay, because our birthdays are technically apart!
Yeah, but mine is February 1st, and mine is on the second... second!
And that's why today's collab stream is right in between, right in between! Makes sense, yeah?
Yeah, smart, yeah! Wow, you know, it's our first ever birthday live!
So, we wanted to have an especially fun time together! That's why the party light, you know?
The good part of the party is always the hashtag! Hashtag! Yeah!
So, please make sure to use our hashtag! Hashtag FWMCbday25 right up here, this way! That's the hashtag, you see it? Don't get it wrong!
And please put your thoughts and screenshots there, and then after everything...
We'll take a look at them after the live! Like... But... But make sure to use the hashtag, Moco-chan!
Woo! Look at our stage! Woo! Wow, bau bau!
And it's so cute! I think things here might be a little bit... sweet, cute. Oh, sweet! Yeah.
Mococo-chan, keep your paws off the damn cake. Ah, no... Not right now! Not yet! Mococo-chan, you're going to take care of the cleanup of the stage? Sans-san will take care of it? Yeah!
Thank you! You know, sweet! And I think we can also get into the... maybe things might be a little bit silly today, too.
Especially with all the fun we have had! Oh, you know, and our special guests... Our special guests! Yeah!
So we hope that you'll cheer us on lots of lots as we sing and dance together with them, okay?
So we hope that you'll cheer us on lots and lots as we sing and dance together with them, okay?
Our next song... We wanted to share a song that's very special to us. A kind that goes back to our roots!
Oh, our roots! Our demon roots! Bau bau!
Fuwamoco? We're they fluffy, fuzzy, buzzy, and silly... but we're demon dogs, you know?
Very hungry demon dogs! We might look cute, but don't doubt our strength, okay? Yeah!
Got it? Please listen to our next song then... Kaiju!
ああ、素晴らしい世界に今日も乾杯
Ah, cheers to this wonderful world today as well.
街に飛び交う笑い声も
Even the laughter echoing through the streets
見て見ぬふりしてるだけの作りもんさ
are just fabricated things turned a blind eye to.
気が触れそうだ
It's driving me crazy.
砕くらくするほどの良い匂いが
A scent so good it makes you melt
ツンと刺した鼻の奥
pierces sharp deep inside the nose.
目を覚ます本能のまま
Guided by awakening instincts,
今日は誰の番だ？
whose turn is it today?
この世界で何が出来るのか
What can be done in this world?
僕には何が出来るのか
What can I possibly do?
ただその真っ黒な目から涙こぼれ落ちないように
So that tears won't spill from those pitch-black eyes,
願う未来に何度でもずっと喰らいつく
I'll keep biting into the future I wish for, no matter how many times.
この間違いだらけの世界の中
In this world full of mistakes,
君には笑ってほしいから
I want you to keep smiling,
もう誰も傷付けない強く強くなりたいんだよ
so I want to become stronger, strong enough never to hurt anyone again.
僕が僕でいられるように
So that I can stay who I am.
素晴らしい世界は今日も安泰
This wonderful world is safe and sound today too.
街に渦巻く悪い話も
Even the malicious rumors swirling through the city,
知らない知らないふりして目を逸らした
I pretended not to know and looked away.
正気の沙汰じゃないな
It's pure madness.
真面目に着飾った行進
A procession dressed up in earnestness.
鳴らす足音が弾む行き先は
Where do the ringing footsteps bound to?
消えない消えない味が染み付いている
An indelible, unforgettable taste is soaked deep inside.
裏側の世界
The world on the flip side.
清く正しく生きること
To live purely and righteously,
誰も悲しませずに生きること
to live without making anyone sad,
はみ出さず真っ直ぐに生きること
to live straight without standing out—
それが間違いないで生きること？
is that really living without making mistakes?
ありのままで生きることが正義か
Is living just as you are justice,
騙し騙し生きるのは正義か
or is living by deceiving justice?
僕の在るべき姿とはなんだ
What is my true form supposed to be?
本当の僕はは何者なんだ
Who on earth am I truly?
教えてくれよ
Somebody tell me.
Please tell me.
今日も答えのない世界の中で
In this world with no answers today either,
足掻いているんだよ不器用だけれど
I'm struggling, even if clumsily.
いつまでも君とただ笑っていたいから
Because I just want to keep smiling with you forever.
跳ねる心臓が身体揺らし叫ぶんだよ今こそ動き出せ
My pounding heart shakes my body and screams: 'Move now!'
弱い自分何度でもずっと喰らいつく
I'll keep biting into my weak self, no matter how many times.
この間違いだらけの世界の中
In this world full of mistakes,
君には笑ってほしいから
I want you to keep smiling,
もう誰も泣かないよう強く強くなりたいんだよ
so I want to become stronger, strong enough so nobody cries anymore.
僕が僕でいられるように
So that I can stay who I am.
ただ君を守るそのために走る走る走るんだよ
To protect you and you alone, I'll run, run, and keep running.
僕の中の僕を超える
Transcending the self inside of me.
口づけさえ 今は 悲しいだけ
Even a kiss right now is just sad.
君の心 どこか 置き去りのまま
Your heart remains left behind somewhere.
口づけさえ 今は 悲しいだけ
Even a kiss right now is just sad.
君の心 どこか 置き去りのまま
Your heart remains left behind somewhere.
当たり前に 見えた あの優しさは
That kindness that seemed so natural
きっと 他の誰ものものになる
will surely belong to someone else.
揺れる心 迷う気持ち どこに置けばいいの？
Shaking heart, hesitating feelings—where should I put them?
重なりを 解いても 古くしかのいの
Even if we untangle our embrace, it's too old now.
あさる 私 孤独 になる 二人きりなのに
Searching inside me, I become alone even though it's just the two of us.
触れた見えない声も届かない
The invisible voice I touched doesn't reach you either.
何もできない私 ただの マリオネット
I can do nothing at all, just a marionette.
君が目指した ディスティネーション
The destination you aimed for,
最後の言葉 スローモーション
your final words in slow motion.
聞きたくない 知りたくもない
I don't want to hear them, I don't want to know.
ちぐはぐになる コンビネーション
A mismatched combination,
泣き出しそうな グラデーション
a tearful graduation.
私 どんな 顔 で いれば いい かな 冗談 だよね
What kind of face should I make? You're just joking, right?
好きだよって言ってよ
Tell me that you love me.
胸にささる 時計は いつからだよ
Since when has that clock been piercing my chest?
見えない壁 それは気づかぬふり
An invisible wall, pretending not to notice.
優しいふり 今更しなくてもいいと
Even if you don't need to act kind anymore,
わかってるのにできないの
even though I know it, I just can't do it.
望む愛は 私ばかりで理解できないもの
The love I wish for is all on my own, something I can't understand.
ほかの誰かでは埋められないもの
Something that can't be filled by anyone else—
疑問さえも多分生ままでできるのに 私動けない
even doubts, perhaps... I can't even move.
強い愛 許せない
Strong love, I can't forgive it.
後悔しちゃう ここから 抑えきれない
I'll regret it. From here on, I can't hold it back!
さよならの場所 インビテーション 行きたくないよ テンプテーション
An invitation to a place of goodbye, a temptation I don't want to go to.
傷ついても そばにいたいよ
Even if I get hurt, I want to stay by your side.
悲しい気持ち キャリブレーション 受け入れないよ レボリューション
Sad feeling calibration, a revolution I won't accept.
強がる ことしか 今はできない 冗談 だよね 嘘だよって言ってよ
All I can do right now is act tough. You're joking, right? Tell me it's a lie.
名前を呼んでも 悪口言っても もう届かない 気づかないの
Even if I call your name or say bad things, it doesn't reach you anymore. Don't you notice?
はにかむ 笑顔は もう ここにはないの ならば 明日は来ないで
Your bashful smile is no longer here. If so, then tomorrow shouldn't come.
君の目指した ディスティネーション
The destination you aimed for,
最後の言葉 スローモーション
your final words in slow motion.
聞きたくない 知りたくもない
I don't want to hear them, I don't even want to know.
ちぐはぐになる コンビネーション
A mismatched combination,
泣き出しそうな グラデーション もう君に
a tearful graduation. I can no longer...
甘えちゃいけないかな 大好きな人 さよならさよなら
lean on you, my dearest person. Goodbye, goodbye.
Ohayou!
The FWMC Party is so high!
You know, FUWAMOCO, we're demon dogs after all, bow-wow!
You get it now, huh?
We hope you enjoyed seeing just a bit more of our power and lots of cute fluff and floof all the time!
And you know, together with Abbit, we were able to sing an idol song that we love called Kanashimi Calibration!
And you know, this whole event has been really, really special to us because it was a song that we wanted to sing together with Abbit all the way back when we were together in the cell.
And fluff-fiends, you call... they were absolutely amazing! Good call! Thank you!
And fluff-fiends, your calls... they were absolutely amazing! Good calls! Thank you!
Destination! Right!
Babehon, you gave us so much power during that last part of our performance there! Thank you, fluff-fiends!
But you know, we showed you a little bite of what these demon dogs have, yeah?
But we want to be able to show the Ruffians lots of different sides of FUWAMOCO today, right? Right!
Outside, all the sides! But the next side...
It's a challenging side, Ruffians! It's going to be a little bit challenging, okay?
You know, FUWAMOCO, we wanted to show a bit more of a...
A railing side.
Maybe a bit more... sexy! Hi-see! Sexy! Yeah? 'Cause you know, FUWAMOCO is sexy, right?
Right? Do I hear your voice?
Yes!
No... No...
Yes! Well!
I'm proving with you, okay?
I'm proving it with you, okay?
Okay, Mococo, say, "You're my best, okay?"
Ooh, but to be able to do that, we prepared some solo songs for you today!
Yay! Pop pop!
Not only is it going to be a bit of a challenge, but it'll be our first time dancing and singing on our own for you! So I...
To tell the truth... I'm a little bit nervous...
Mococo's nervous? I know right, never happened!
So I'll do my best, but you need to make sure you give me lots of headpats, okay? I like headpats too! Yeah! Okay!
Well, um, I'm too nervous right now. Okay, Mococo, whose live is going to go?
No? I choose now. Wh- Wh- Who goes first? Huh? Yeah!
Okay, well... Mococo, you have to go after though, okay? I guess.
What else are you gonna do otherwise? Ha! Yeah! Do your best, okay?
Okay! Bye-bye! Pop pop!
Well, for Fuwawa's... I guess it's time for me to take you back a few years with this next song. Please listen to "Mugon... Iroppoi".
言えないのよ
I can't say it
言いたいことならどれくらい
I don't know how much I want to say
あるか分からなくてあふれてる
So it's all spilling out
私心は
My heart
おしゃべりだわ
is a blabbermouth
言いたいことならあなたには
What I want to say to you
あとからあとからあふれてる
Keeps spilling out, one after another
私意外と
Turns out
おしゃべりだわ
I'm quite a talker
なのにいざとなると内気になる
But when it comes down to it, I get shy
遠い場所から何度も話しかけてるのに
Even though I've talked to you so many times from far away
目と目で通じ合う
We communicate with our eyes
かすかに、ん、色っぽい
And it's mm, sexy in a subtle way
目と目で通じ合う
We communicate with our eyes
そういう仲になりたいわ
I wish we had the kind of relationship
無言育じなしね
Silence is a coward
無言淋しがりね
Silence is lonely
言いたいことならあの日から
Ever since that day, what I want to say
誰にも負けずにあふれてる
Has been spilling out, beating out everyone else
私、気持ちは
I'm so selfish
わがままだわ
about my feelings
なのにいざとなると
But when it comes down to it,
内気になる
I get shy
書いた手紙もしまい込んで
I tuck away the letter I wrote—
誰も知らない
nobody will know
目と目で通じ合う
We communicate with our eyes
かすかに、ん、色っぽい
And it's mm, sexy in a subtle way
目と目で通じ合う
We communicate with our eyes
そういう仲になりたいわ
I wish we had the kind of relationship
明日少し勇気をだして
Tomorrow I think I'll be a little braver
視線投げてみようかしら
And cast a glance your way
目と目で通じ合う
We communicate with our eyes
かすかに、ん、色っぽい
And it's mm, sexy in a subtle way
目と目で通じ合う
We communicate with our eyes
そういう仲になりたいわ
I wish we had the kind of relationship
明日少し勇気をだして
Tomorrow I think I'll be a little braver
視線投げてみようかしら
And cast a glance your way
目と目で通じ合う
We communicate with our eyes
かすかに、ん、色っぽい
And it's mm, sexy in a subtle way
目と目で通じ合う
We communicate with our eyes
そういう仲になりたいわ
I wish we had the kind of relationship
無言育じなしね
Silence is a coward
無言淋しがりね
Silence is lonely
無言育じなしね
Silence is a coward
無言淋しがりね
Silence is lonely
言えないのよ
I can't say it
筋肉を触らせてよ
Let me feel your muscles!
どんな感じなのかな
I wonder what they feel like?
興味があるのよ
I'm so curious!
女の子って不思議だね
Boys are so mysterious, aren't they?
今日のバッグなんだか重くて
Today's bag is a bit heavy,
そう 誰かに持って欲しかった
so I wanted someone to hold it for me.
だからちょっと頭を絞って
That's why I racked my brain a little
ハートを釣ってみたの
and tried to hook your heart!
甘いため息ひとつ
With a single sweet sigh,
チラリと見て
taking a quick peek,
おねだりするの
I'll coax you.
わるきー
Warukii~
筋肉を触らせてよ
Let me feel your muscles!
どれくらい固いの？
How hard are they?
女の子には興味津々
Girls are always so curious,
たくましさ見てみたいのよ
wanting to see your strength.
どんな感じなのかな
What's it like?
わくわくしてるわ
It makes me so excited!
上腕二頭筋ってセクシーだね
Your biceps are so sexy!
これを持って！
Hold this!
男らしいマッチョがタイプよ
Manly, macho guys are my type,
でもホントはそんなことないけど…
but the truth is, not really...
じっと見つめおだててあげなくちゃ
I gotta stare and flatter you nicely,
何にも釣れないわ
or I won't catch anything at all!
こっちが頼んじゃいなくてやらせてくれて頼まれるように…
Making you want to do it for me without me even asking...
わるきー
Warukii~
筋肉に抱かれたいの
I want to be held by your muscles
いつのかどこかで
someday, somewhere.
私のために頑張って
Work hard for my sake!
筋肉に抱かれたいの折れるくらい強く
Held by muscles, so strong they might break me—
胸が熱くなるよ
my chest gets so hot!
腹筋だって割れてるし…
Your abs are even toned and split...
これも持って！
Hold this too!
You really are mysterious, aren't you?
Or maybe it's just that...
I like experimenting more!
Hey, won't you help me get past my embarrassment?
髪をかきあげながら
As I brush my hair back,
試すように反応見るわ
I'll test your reaction.
わるきー
Warukii~
筋肉を触らせてよ
Let me feel your muscles!
どれくらい固いの？
How hard are they?
女の子には興味津々
Girls are always so curious,
たくましさ見てみたいのよ
wanting to see your strength.
どんな感じなのかな
What's it like?
わくわくしてるわ
It makes me so excited!
上腕二頭筋ってセクシーだね
Your biceps are so sexy!
全部持って！
Hold it all!
Oh no, Mokocchan's time is ending!
Well then, can you close your eyes for me?
Hey, why are you peeking?
Gosh!
Wow-wow!
えー？
"Huh?"
ぽいず？
"Poiz?"
いや、違え、いや、違え！
"No, wait, no, that's not it!"
えー、おみ、フワモコと曲をやろうよ、フワモコじゃ！
"Wait, Omi, let's do a song with Fuwamoco, Fuwamoco..."
えー？もしかして、最初の曲ができるの初めてじゃ？えー？
"Huh? Could this be our very first time doing a song? Huh?"
えっ、ゲットー、スペシャルなレッスンからー、ある特定の先輩！
"Huh? Ge— from a special lesson, a certain senior!"
おいー！
"Hey!"
えーとね、この先輩、あたし、もっとー、一番、あの、セクシーなネスの、クィーンなセクシーネス！
"Um, you know, this senior, I think she's definitely the queen of sexiness—sexiness!"
レッツゴー、呼ぼう！
"Let's call her on! Okay!"
まいりーせんせー、さーん、ぱーい！
"Marine-sensei, sen-pai!"
お前たち、セクシーになりたいんですって？
"You guys want to be sexy?"
そうー、さっきほら、その曲、どうだった、モコちゃんとー、なんか、セクシーしててー、うん。
"That's right, earlier, you know, how was that song? Mococo and I were being kind of sexy, yeah."
え？なになにしてるんですか？
"Eh? What are you guys doing?"
まあまあまあ、まあまあ、セクシーー、全体的なスタイル！
"Well, you know, sexy—overall style!"
しっぽ、しっぽ触っちゃダメですよ、先輩！
"You mustn't touch tails, senpai!"
なんでダメなの？
"Why is that bad?"
だめだめだめ！なんでダメなの？
"No, no, no! Why is that bad?"
なんて？
"What?"
いや、ダメなのよ！ダメって！ダメダメダメですよ、先輩！
"I mean, it's no good! It's no good! No, no, no, senpai!"
だめかー！
"Aw, no good!"
え、じゃあどうすれば？
"Eh, then what should we do?"
もっこはもっとセクシーになれますか？
"Can Mococo become even sexier?"
そうですね、じゃあ、ちょっとセクシーショットを今から撮っていきましょう！オッケー！じゃあ、カメラ用意しますねー！
"Let's see, then let's take some sexy shots right now! Okay! Then, I'll get the camera ready!"
はい、チーズ！
"Say cheese!"
あ、もしもしちゃった！あ、もしもしして！
"Ah, we touched! Ah, touch!"
おい、それ船長ボードだぞ！勝手に被るな！
"Hey, that's the captain's board! Don't wear it without asking!"
まんざら…まんざら？
"You're liking it... liking it?"
え、これセクシーなのかな？え、セクシー？いや、これセクシーじゃないね！
"Eh, is this sexy? Eh, sexy? No, this isn't sexy!"
はい、行きます！
"Alright, here we go!"
え、ちょっと待って、ちょっと待って！
"Eh, wait a second, wait a second!"
も、も、もう一回！
"On, on, once more!"
もっこちゃん、あ、モコちゃん逃げてた！
"Mococo-chan, ah, Mococo-chan ran away!"
じゃあ、じゃあ、ほな、ほなフワワは、フワワは、え？フワワもダメです！あ、ダメですか？やめて！先輩！
"Then, then, well, then Fuwawa, Fuwawa, eh? Fuwawa is no good either! Ah, is it no good? Stop it! Senpai!"
まんざら！
"You're liking it!"
じゃあ、もう一回！じゃあ、はい、オッケーじゃあ！
"Then, once more! Then, yeah, okay!"
もう一回！一緒に！
"Once more! Together!"
あ、モコちゃん、これ、あの、モコちゃんが考えるセクシーポーズって何？
"Ah, Mococo-chan, what is this, um, sexy pose that Mococo-chan thinks of?"
確かに！
"True!"
みっしー、にゃー！にゃあ！にゃあ！万の味はあると思いますけど…
"Missy, nya! Nya! Nya! I think there are tens of thousands of tastes, but..."
じゃあ、最後に3、2、1でアホイ！
"Then, finally, at 3, 2, 1, Ahoy!"
アホイ！はい！
"Ahoy! Yes!"
うん、オッケー！オッケー！じゃあ、3、2、1！アホイ！
"Yeah, okay! Okay! Then, 3, 2, 1! Ahoy!"
ふー！がんばった！がんばったがんばった！
"Woo! We did our best! We did our best!"
え、みんな覚えてる？
"Eh, does everyone remember?"
何？今日はライブなんです！
"What? Today is a live!"
あ、そうだ！今日はライブだよね！
"Ah, that's right! Today is a live!"
こんなことしてる場合じゃない！
"This isn't the time to be doing this!"
We're here on stage, right!
We'll sing one of our favorite songs by Marine Senpai!
じゃあ、いきましょうか！せーの！アホイ！宝鐘海賊団！
"Well, shall we go? Ready, go! Ahoy! Houshou Marine Pirates!"
Ahoy!! 我ら宝鐘海賊団☆
Ahoy!! We are the Houshou Pirates☆
海賊なら Yo-Ho! 踊れ叫べ Yo-Ho!
If you're pirates, Yo-Ho! Dance and shout, Yo-Ho!
さあみんなで宝鐘海賊団！
Come on, everyone, the Houshou Pirates!
出港！
Set sail!
Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!
踊る Ahoy! に見る Ahoy!
Dancing Ahoy! Seeing Ahoy!
全身全霊で進め！
Advance with all your body and soul!
大洋は燦々 毎口（まいか）海日よりだ
The ocean is brilliant, every day is a pirate sunny day!
歌え！最高のテンション 波の音に乗せ丼ぶり感情
Sing! With the highest tension, riding the sound of waves like a donburi emotion!
海で Girls Party おかれ 兄貴が Happy 船内では読書苦？
A girls' party on the sea, bros are happy, is reading hard on ship?
キラキラ 山をくぼろ、マイハウスで夢を見て
Sparkling, digging through mountains, dreaming in my house—
山おくボロボロ マイハウスで夢を見て
Deep in the tattered mountains, dreaming in my house,
あー 神様！いつかこのフワモコを本物の海賊にしてくだちゃい！
Ah, God! Someday, please make this Fuwamoco real pirates!
声を上げてさあ出港だ 我ら宝鐘海賊団！
Raise your voices and set sail! We are the Houshou Pirates!
コンパス片手に旗を掲げ この海をジャックしちゃお！
Compass in hand, raise the flag and jack this sea!
一同そろって おいでおいで 共にYo-Ho! Yo-Ho! 叫ぼう！
Everyone gather 'round, come on, let's shout Yo-Ho! Yo-Ho! together!
最高の日は ようこそ我がへ
Welcome to the best day of our home—
Ahoy!
Ahoy! Ahoy!
Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!
Ahoy!
踊るAhoy! 見るAhoy!
Dancing Ahoy! Seeing Ahoy!
Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!
1, 2, サンバ！サンバ！
One, two, samba, samba!
熱く！熱く！揺らめくPassion！
Hot, hot, Red Passion!
想いを解き放て
Unleash your feelings!
赤く！赤く！揺らめくFashion！
Red, red, trembling fashion!
形から入るタイプです！
The type that enters from form!
発射10秒前！
Hurry, 10 seconds before!
走れ！ガチ恋でしょ？
Run, let's fall in love!
受け止めれるわ キラキラ☆
Can you catch it? Sparkling!
ずんわり汗もしてたタルい女だけど...
A gentle girl who sweats a bit, but...
あぁ、神様 船長はセンシティブだと
Ah, Captain, if you are sensitive,
BANされちゃうのですねー！
you will be banned!
はにゃー！
Hanya-!
奪われたら取り戻せ
If it's stolen, take it back!
それが宝鐘海賊団な！
That's the Houshou Pirates' code!
君たちとならたどり着ける
Reaching the destination with you!
伝説のエルドラド！
The legendary El Dorado!
夜空ろ楽しけりゃ歌えよ Ho-Ho-
Everyone, let's have fun and sing!
Ho-Ho- 足りない ああ この景色
Not enough, ah! This scenery is...
大切 なかまよ
So precious!
歌えーど 歌えーど
Singing! Singing!
騒げや騒げ！
Making a fuss! Making a fuss!
踊るAhoy! 見るAhoy!
Dancing Ahoy! Seeing Ahoy!
Ahoy! Ahoy!
同じAhoy! ならのまでか3, 3, 3!
Same Ahoy! The same deck, 1, 2, 3!
方角片手にいきますよ、それ！
With a compass in hand, let's go!
Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!
宝鐘マリン！宝鐘マリン！
Houshou Marine! Houshou Marine!
世界で一番かわいいよ！
The cutest in the world!
メガネきメガネき メガネきメガネき
Megane, megane! Megane, megane!
エロガキエロガキ エロガキエロガキ
Erogaki, erogaki! Erogaki, erogaki!
ワンキューワンキュー ワンキューワンキュー
Wanqiu, wanqiu! Wanqiu, wanqiu!
パスのみろ シムシムショウ！
Pass the miro! Shimu shimu show!
おったかよ おったかよ
Otsukare! Otsukare!
まざい！まざい！まざい！まざい！
Mazai! Mazai! Mazai! Mazai!
なでまつどん！なでまつどん！
Nadematsu-don! Nadematsu-don!
船長のちょっといそっかい！いんたい！
Captain's a little impatient! Insane!
もっと！もっと！うふふ、うふふ！
More! More! Uh-huh, uh-huh!
もっと！もっと！SEXY BEAM!
More! More! Sexy beam!
もっと！もっと！ヤンマイシン！
More! More! Yang-machine!
もっと！もっと！ダチュノエ！
More! More! Tachinoye!
もっと！もっと！サビサビスー！
More! More! Sabisabisu!
もっと！もっと！もえもえキュン！
More! More! Moemoe-kyun!
出会って5秒で即出航～！！！
Meet in 5 seconds and immediate departure!
あぁ、もう 船長は君たちのそんな子に育ったと覚えるはありません
Ah, Captain doesn't remember
本当に？ねぇ、だったぞ
Really? Really?
立ち位置も座る場所も
Where we stand, where we sit,
歩く姿は日々違う
the way we walk are all different days.
夢を見よう この船で
Let's see our dreams on this ship,
後悔なんてさせない
we can never say regret!
君たちのおかげで私は船長になれるから
Thanks to you, I can become a captain!
テイクオフ船長キャノン！撃てぇー！
Get ready, Captain cannon! Fire!
声を上げてさあ出航だ
Voices raised for immediate departure!
我ら宝鐘海賊団
That's the Houshou Pirates' code!
コンパス片手に旗を上げ
Compass in one hand, flag raised,
この海をジャックしちゃおう
let's make this ocean yours and mine!
夜空ろついておいで
Everyone, follow along, come here,
共にHo-Ho- 叫ぼう
and shout together, ho-ho-!
あぁ 最期の君
Ah, for you, my dearest,
永遠とは 我が船へ
forevermore, our ship is...
宝鐘の海賊団
The Houshou Pirates!
それでは行きますよ！
Now then, let's go!
出航！ヨ〜ソロ〜！
Departure! Yo-ho-ro!
Welcome to ようこそ ジャパリパーク！
Welcome to Japari Park!
今日もドッタンバッタン大騒ぎ
Let's rock and uproar today, too!
うー！がー！
Grrr roar!
ようこそジャパリパークへ
Welcome to Japari Park!
はじめまして
Nice to meet you!
うー！がー！
Grrr roar!
振り返ればあちらこちらでトラブル
Looking back and everywhere I see,
（トラブル）
troubles!
喧嘩してすれちがいまっかちがっても仲良し
Even if we fight and make up,
けものはいてものけものはいない
Animals are animals, let it go!
本当の愛はここにある
The true love is right here!
ほら 君も手を繋いで大冒険
Look, you, too, hold hands
（わん・つー・すりー）
(One, two, three)
Welcome to ようこそ ジャパリパーク！
Welcome to Japari Park!
今日もドッタンバッタン大騒ぎ
Let's rock and uproar today, too!
姿かたちも十人十色
There are different appearances for everyone,
だから魅かれ合うの
so we get attracted to each other!
夕暮れ空に 指をそっと重ねたら
When I put my fingers into the setting sun,
はじめまして
Nice to meet you!
君をもっと知りたいな
I want to know more about you!
うー！がー！
Grrr roar!
振り返ればあちらこちらでトラブル
Look back and everywhere I see, troubles!
（トラブル）
Troubles!
なんてこった てんでバラバラ ちんぷんかんぷん
What the heck, bang holler guffaw!
まとまんない
It doesn't get settled!
Welcome to ようこそジャパリパーク！
Welcome to Japari Park!
今日も ドッタンバッタン 大騒ぎ
Today is also full of commotion!
うー！ がうー！
Grrr, roar!
高らかに 笑い笑えば フレンズ
Laugh loudly and we're friends,
喧騒して すっちゃかめちゃかしてても 仲良し
even if we make a ruckus, we're best friends.
はい、どうぞ
Here we go!
Nice to meet you ジャパリパーク！
Nice to meet you at Japari Park!
今日からは どうぞ よろしくね
Please treat us well starting today!
いつもいつでも 優しい笑顔 君を待っていたの
Always waiting for you with a tender smile.
開かれた 扉 夢をいっぱい語ったら
Once we open the door and talk about our dreams,
どこまでも どこまでも 続いてく
it will continue on and on, anywhere,
グレートジャーニー
our great journey.
東へ 吠えろ 西へ 吠えろ
Howl to the east, howl to the west,
世界中に 響け サファリメロディ
sound the safari melody all over the world!
Welcome to ようこそ ジャパリパーク！
Welcome to Japari Park!
今日も ドッタンバッタン 大騒ぎ
Today is also full of commotion!
姿形も 十人十色 だから 魅かれ合うの
Everyone is unique, which is why we're drawn to each other.
夕暮れ空に 指をそっと重ねたら
When we softly overlap our fingers in the twilight sky,
はじめまして 君をもっと知りたいな
nice to meet you, I want to know more about you.
うー！ がうー！
Grrr, roar!
ララララ… Oh, welcome to the Japari park!
La la la... Oh, welcome to the Japari Park!
ララララ… 集まれ 友達
La la la... Gather around, friends!
Oh, welcome to the Japari park!
素敵な 旅立ち
A wonderful journey,
ようこそ ジャパリパーク！
welcome to Japari Park!
あらゆる困難が科学で解決するこの平成の時代
In this Heisei era where all hardships are solved by science,
人々の閉ざされた心の闇に蔓延る
rampant in the closed-off darkness of people's hearts,
魑魅魍魎が 存在していた
monsters and spirits existed.
科学の力ではどうしようも出来ないその奇奇怪怪な妖怪に立ち向かう
Facing those bizarre apparitions that science couldn't handle,
神妙不可思議にて胡散臭い男がひとり
stands one mysterious, uncanny, and shady man.
その名は 矢部野彦麿
His name is Hikomaro Yabeno.
そう 人は彼を陰陽師と呼ぶ
Yes, people call him an Onmyoji—
悪霊退散！悪霊退散！
Exorcise evil spirits! Exorcise evil spirits!
怨霊 ものの怪 困った時は ドーマン！セーマン！ドーマン！セーマン！
When troubled by vengeful spirits and phantoms, Doman! Seeman! Doman! Seeman!
直ぐに呼びましょう陰陽師 レッツゴー！
Call the Onmyoji right away, let's go!
死してなお この世に未練残せしは
Those who leave behind attachments to this world even in death,
魑魅魍魎と成り果て その悪しき血を清めるが
turning into ghouls and spirits, to purify that evil blood—
陰陽の道
the path of Yin and Yang!
人の世に生まれし悪を闇にへと葬れよ
Banish the evil born in the world of men into the darkness!
悪霊退散！悪霊退散！
Exorcise evil spirits! Exorcise evil spirits!
妖怪 あやかし 困った時は ドーマン！セーマン！ドーマン！セーマン！
When troubled by specters and apparitions, Doman! Seeman! Doman! Seeman!
助けてもらおう陰陽師 レッツゴー！
Let's ask the Onmyoji for help, let's go!
生きながら 怨み惜しみ 妬りしは 悪鬼悪霊
Those who harbor resentment and jealousy while alive are evil demons and spirits.
呼び覚ます その激昂を宥めるも
To soothe that awakening rage—
陰陽の道 愛しさの
the path of Yin and Yang, of love...
行き着く果てに 病む魂
At the end of the journey, a sick soul
慰めよ 悪鬼悪霊
be comforted, evil demons and spirits!
悪霊退散！悪霊退散！
Exorcise evil spirits! Exorcise evil spirits!
怨念 怨恨 困った時は ドーマン！セーマン！ドーマン！セーマン！
When troubled by grudges and spite, Doman! Seeman! Doman! Seeman!
鎮めてもらおう陰陽師 レッツゴー！
Have the Onmyoji pacify them, let's go!
辛い時 悲しい時は
When things are tough, when you're sad,
人はそんな時 心の隙間に闇ができる
that's when darkness forms in the gaps of people's hearts.
その心の闇に魔物達は容赦なく入り込んでくるのだ！
Into the darkness of that heart, monsters ruthlessly come creeping in!
だから苦しくてもくじけるな！
So even if it's painful, don't give up!
落ち込むな！
Don't get down!
くよくよするな！
Don't fret!
何事にも屈しない強靭な心こそが最強の武器なのだから！
Because an indomitable heart that yields to nothing is your strongest weapon!
ゆらめく心
Wavering hearts...
心を狙うもの 打ち砕け！
Smash those who target the heart!
悪霊退散！悪霊退散！
Begone, evil spirits! Begone, evil spirits!
超常現象 困った時は ドーマン！セーマン！ドーマン！セーマン！
When troubled by supernatural phenomena, Doman! Seeman! Doman! Seeman!
祓ってもらおう 陰陽師 レッツゴー！悪霊退散！悪霊退散！
Let's have them exorcised by an Onmyoji, Let's Go! Begone, evil spirits!
呪い呪われ 困った時は ドーマン！セーマン！ドーマン！セーマン！
When troubled by curses and being cursed, Doman! Seeman! Doman! Seeman!
相談しましょう 陰陽師 レッツゴー！やっぱり頼れる 陰陽師 レッツゴー！
Let's consult an Onmyoji, Let's Go! As expected, you can rely on an Onmyoji, Let's Go!
みんなのヒーロー 陰！陽！師！
Everyone's hero, Yin! Yang! Master!
成仏しろよ！
Rest in peace!
BAW BAW! Hi guys!
Welcome to our birthday party together with us, right?
You know, we have some of our holodog senpai joining us right here.
Welcome to "Yappari! Party", an extra special version of "Let's Go! Onmyoji", right?
What was that with the bells and the microphone?
Well, you know, that's the necessary part of "Let's Go! Onmyoji", right?
I guess.
We're just so happy to have a bunch of our friends here with us for a big birthday live today.
It's been really special so far, huh? Yeah!
But, but, we're still not done! We've got another surprise for you.
What? Is the fun time already over, though? No, not time, right?
Yeah! Well, Ruffians, you know, it's our special day today, but actually, we have something we'd like to surprise you with!
Are you ready? Okay, then drumroll. Okay. 3, 2, 1!
Our birthday merch today! Here we have a FUWAMOCO birthday set and MOCOCO birthday set.
Well, this year's birthday merch is a little bit embarrassing.
I'm sure it's going to be okay, Fuwawa. It's going to be okay. I know a lot of Ruffians have been waiting for a long time for something like this, but...
Ta-da! Here we have the definitive FUWAMOCO dakimakura cover!
But in a way, right, you know, Ruffians, you can't just have Fuwawa on one side and me on the other, okay? That's not okay. Got it?
Yeah! So that's why we have a Fuwawa version and a Mococo version! Of course with a beautiful illustration, but I love...
Fuwamoco Birthday merchandise is finally here!
This is the Fuwawa Dakimakura!
And here is the Mococo Dakimakura!
The body pillow is embarrassing, but...
We hope that we can help you sleep soundly
at night, you know!
Fuwawa hugging version, and Mococo hugging version!
Even though it might be a little bit embarrassing,
we hope that we can help you sleep soundly at night!
Fuwawa & Mococo Hugging Body Pillow Cover!
And next, we have Fuwawa Plushie Keychain!
Mococo Plushie Keychain, compact size!
Fuwawa Mascot can go anywhere, and anywhere along with you!
Attached to your bag, maybe your keys,
maybe even your car!
No matter what, we'll be by your side, and super cute!
And next, we have a very cute Fuwawa Headband and Mococo Headband!
Maybe you're wondering, what exactly is this?
Well, this way we can help keep back the fluff in the face
when you wash your face at night!
Or maybe you can just have fun with a quick Fuwamoskyle disguise!
And finally, we have some cute collectible Button Badges of Fuwawa and Mococo!
That's sparkly and holographic, and come in a super cute heart shape!
It's perfect for any ita-bags, you know, just bringing a bit more Fuwamoco to your belongings!
But uh, well, we also have something special as well, right Mococo?
Something more special! Yeah, you know what would help you get an even better rest at night, right?
Voice pack! A soothing Sleepover with Fuwawa ASMR voice, and a soothing Sleepover with Mococo ASMR voice!
But we hope that you'll listen to both of them right before bed!
And finally, for fans who purchase the entire set, we also have a special thank you bonus voice message as well!
And of course, there are also special hand-signed limited edition sets!
That come with a Polaroid-style card! Wow, so cute!
We really hope that you'll be able to get your paws on them as well, ruffians!
And as a full set bonus, you'll receive one card that can be used in the Hololive Official Card Game! One card for Fuwawa's set, one card for Mococo's set!
And this card is only available to those who purchase from the Hololive Production official shop!
Okay, got it? Please look forward to it, okay?
You know, after that very exciting announcement...
We still have one last song we'd like to sing for you today!
This next song is one that's really important to us, especially when we were still locked up back in the cell.
And now that we're finally a part of Hololive, and you know, we're even able to have our first ever birthday live!
We'd like to sing it for you, okay? Please listen. Kirameki Rider☆!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats echo!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best friends,
キラメキに乗って☆
Riding on the sparkle☆
イエーイ！
Yay!
覚えてるかな 最初の一曲
Do you remember our very first song?
私声が震えていた (ほんの少し)
My voice was trembling (just a little bit).
あの日から続く未来は みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
The future that started from that day is today we seized together with everyone!
もっともっともっともっと 加速するハート
More and more, my heart accelerates!
(いっしょに) 行くよどこまでも
(Together) Let's go anywhere!
(are you ready?) 準備はOK？
(Are you ready?) Are you all set?
ひらけ！！ 夢のトビラを (1 2 3)
Open up!! The door of dreams (1 2 3)
アイまり準備はOK？
Are you ready? We're all set, OK?
ひらけ!! 夢の ドビラを
Open the doors into our crazy dreams!
1, 2, 3 キラメキライダー☆
(One, two, three, Kirameki Rider!)
生まれたての ドドキを 響かせよう
Can you hear all our heartbeats echo for a brand-new start?
最高の時間 最高の 仲間と
Anytime, anyplace, anyone can join on the fun.
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
Now we're here, and you found me where I belong.
きみに 会いたくて やってきたんだ
That's why I came here to see you.
みんなで歌おう
Sing it together now,
終わらない メロディ キラメキに 乗って☆
A never-ending melody, riding on the sparkles...
イエーイ
Yay!
届いてるかな? 私の声
Now I wonder if my voice will reach you in the end?
きっと 届きたいのは きみに笑顔
What can I do to see a smile from a friend?
すこしでも 理想 の 音さに くやしくて
Though the ideal is oh so far out of reach,
みうな とき は 笑ったね
We cried and laughed all of the pain away.
ぎゅっと ぎゅっと ぎゅっと ぎゅっと すべて抱きしめて
Never ever, ever letting go, holding all of it close.
いっしょに行こう どこまでも
Let's go wherever we want, you and me.
アイまり準備は OK?
Yeah, we're all set, okay?
すすめ!! 希望 の 道を
Let's walk the road to hope where we belong.
1, 2, 3 キラメキライダー☆
(One, two, three, Kirameki Rider!)
好きな気持ち カラフルに 奏でたいな
Every color you see in the rainbow you can use to paint your dream.
最高の場所 最高の みんな と
Anytime, any place, anyone can join the team.
ここにいるよ 幻 なんかじゃない
I'm right here, this is not an illusion.
きみのココロ が 幸せに染まるように
Turning your heart into a million colors, see all the joy you make.
重ねてく ハーモニー キラメキ まとって☆
Like when we layer harmonies, wrapped in sparkles...
歌い続けたいな 踊り続けたいな
Maybe I can keep on singing, maybe I can keep on dancing.
そんな願い や ワガママも いいでしょ?
Grant me this one wish 'cause sometimes I want what I want.
だって 楽しすぎて もトまらない 輝く ステージ で
Praying all this fun we're having, it will never end and shine forevermore.
もっと もっと!
More and more!
(お願い) ずっと! イエーイ
(Pretty please?) Forever! (Woah, yay)
嬉しい 楽しい いとしい だけじゃ 語れない
All the joy, happiness, and the love isn't enough for how I feel.
今も 今も 悩む は ある けど
Pain will come, and will go, but I know that it will be healed.
ここにいるよ 私ここにいるよ
Am here, don't you see I am standing here in front of you.
きみ と 同じ 世界 を 見つめて 行くよ!
I see the world that you can see with my own two eyes.
キラメキライダー☆
Kirameki Rider!
生まれたての ドドキを 響かせよう
Can you hear? Can you hear all the heartbeats
最高の時間 最高の 仲間 と
Echo for a brand-new start?
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
Now we're here, and you found me where I belong.
きみに 会いたくて やってきたんだ
That's why I came here to see you.
みんなで歌おう
Sing it together now,
終わらない メロディ
A never-ending melody,
キラメキに 乗って☆
riding on the sparkles...
キラメキ まとって☆
wrapped in sparkles...
イエーイ
Yay!
今、あなたの声が聴ける
Right now, I hear your voice
「ここにおいで」と
Saying "come here to me."
今 あなたの声が聴こえる
Right now, I hear your voice
「ここにおいで」と
Saying "Come here to me."
寂しさに 負けそうな わたしに
To me, who seemed ready to lose to loneliness...
今 あなたの姿が見える
Right now, I can see your figure
歩いてくる
Walking toward me.
目を閉じて 待っている わたしに
To me, waiting with my eyes closed...
昨日まで 涙でくもってた
Until yesterday, clouded in tears...
心は今……
My heart is now...
おぼえていますか 目と目が合った時を
Do you remember when our eyes met?
おぼえていますか 手と手が触れあった時
Do you remember when our hands touched?
それは初めての 愛の旅立ちでした
That was the very first journey of love.
I love you, so
今 あなたの視線感じる
Right now, I feel your gaze
離れてても
Even when we're apart
体中が 暖かくなるの
My whole body becomes warm.
今 あなたの愛信じます
Right now, I believe in your love
どうぞ私を
Please, watch over me
遠くから 見守って下さい
From far away.
昨日まで 涙でくもってた
Until yesterday, clouded in tears...
世界は今……
The world is now...
おぼえていますか 目と目が合った時を
Do you remember when our eyes met?
おぼえていますか 手と手が触れあった時
Do you remember when our hands touched?
それは初めての 愛の旅立ちでした
That was the very first journey of love.
I love you, so
もう ひとりぼっちじゃない
I'm not all alone anymore
あなたが いるから
Because you are here with me.
おぼえていますか 目と目が合った時を
Do you remember when our eyes met?
おぼえていますか 手と手が触れあった時
Do you remember when our hands touched?
それは初めての 愛の旅立ちでした
That was the very first journey of love.
I love you, so
もう ひとりぼっちじゃない
I'm not all alone anymore
あなたが いるから
Because you are here with me.
もう ひとりぼっちじゃない
I'm not all alone anymore
あなたが いるから
Because you are here with me.
もう ひとりぼっちじゃない
I'm not all alone anymore
あなたが いるから
Because you are here with me.
Oh, hi! Bau Bau!
Thank you so much for the... Oh, thank you! Bau Bau!
It was really special, you know!
We kept you waiting, though. So, I am all out.
But it means a lot, though.
Really, thank you!
Bau Bau!
Wow, this has been an unforgettable first visit with Ruffian, though!
That was such a forever and ever. I don't know.
Ah, Ruffian. Huh?
I'm a little bit hungry, you know, Mukocchao?
Don't you feel a little hungry after singing and dancing all those songs, though?
But you know, right now, and Mukocchao, we're going to...
Can we just have a quick bite?
It's okay. Love for you.
You don't mind, right? Just a little bite.
Okay. Okay! Bau Bau!
Itadakimasu! Itadakimasu!
Oh, bow wow, bow wow! So yummy!
Mukocchao, this is the time for this!
Well, my tummy's all full now. So, let's do this afterwards, you know?
I guess we do have some more important stuff to talk about, though.
Okay, let's go!
Hey!
Ah, wait. Mukocchao.
I think there's so cream on your face, too.
Right over here.
Hey, you're eating it, though. You know!
It's weird. Huh?
More, you still have cream on your face, too.
So, I mean, wait.
Just one moment. We'll just get it all.
Wow. What was that? My birthday right?
We're super happy to be able to share and perform some of our favorite songs in YouTube today, as well as show lots of different sides of our solus idols.
We put our all into our performance stage, you know?
I laughed and there were flies, sweat and tears, but most importantly, so much of my love.
So, we hope they're able to shine just even a little bit, and we hope...
Continue to do our best. So, please continue to cheer lots for us, okay?
We'll do our best to go into even stronger, even guard dogs, so we'll protect your smile, okay?
Don't take your eyes off us, and we'll continue to keep an eye on you, too, okay?
Wow, with that, we'd like to go into our final final song for today.
But before, for the Ruffian, you're all part of our membership, the doggipark. Have you joined?
Well, we still have a few more songs we'd like to sing, from IHeights to yours.
Yeah, you know, just a little height to height. So, we hope don't... Don't run off. Don't go anywhere after this, okay?
Just do a little more we'd like to share with you, got it?
Well, please wait a little bit while we wipe off some of our sweat and fix ourselves and fuss a little, okay?
But, you know, in the meantime, maybe you can get your paws on some of our birthday merch as well, please wait.
We're really, thank you so much for the love.
We'll continue to do our all, so let's continue on this great journey together, okay?
Well, this last song is especially dear to us, and has kept us going when times have been tough, too.
We know and hope that you'll know we'll always be here for you, and that someone out there will be always waiting. So, dear best...
Well then, please listen to our last song, "Yume no Baton".
聞いた この世界のどこかに
I've heard somewhere in this world
君だけを
Only you...
ふわふわ
Fuwawa!
もこもこ
Mococo!
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★ この世界に爆誕 “BAU”DOL です
Underworld Watchdog Sisters☆★ Bursting into this world as a "BAU"DOL!
baubau ! !
Baubau!!
wake up したら
When I wake up,
君 に morning
saying "morning" to you,
new な 出会い
searching for new encounters
鼻 利か せ search し て
with my nose on high alert—
ドキ ドキ
pounding,
doggy
右 に
To the right,
左
to the left,
bau bau bau
煩ん でいて も 来 ちゃう future
Even if I worry about the future,
まずは 目 の 前 の 道 step し て
first, I'll step onto the path right before me!
happy lucky puppy
一緒に 歩こう よ
let's walk together!
ドーナツ の 穴 の 中 に は
Inside the hole of the donut,
きっと きっと 夢 が 詰まってる から
I'm sure, I'm sure dreams are packed inside!
ふわふわ
Fuwawa!
（wa ! ! foo ! !）
(Wa!! Foo!!)
もこもこ
Mococo!
（come on ! !）
(Come on!!)
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Underworld Watchdog Sisters☆★
2 匹 が 揃え ば もう 大騒ぎ
When the two of us get together, total chaos!
もあ もあ
Moa moa!
（motto ! !）
(More!!)
ハロハロ
Halo halo!
（baubau ! !）
(Baubau!!)
迷わ ず に go my way
Without hesitating, go my way!
君 の 絶対 味方 “BAU”DOL です
I'm your absolute ally, the "BAU"DOL!
きっ と この 世界 の どこ か に
I'm sure, somewhere in this world,
君 だけ を ずっと 待ってる 人 が いる
someone is waiting all alone just for you!
誰 に も 振り回さ れ ない で
Don't let anyone push you around—
君 だけ の 好き や ときめき に 素直 でいて
stay true to your own unique likes and thrills!
そっ と 差し出し た 夢 の バトン
The baton of dreams we gently handed out...
確か に 受け取っ た よ あの 時 に
I definitely received it back then!
駅前 の ベンチ に 座っ て
Sitting on the bench in front of the station,
感情 すっからかん に 未来 を 見つめ てた
staring blankly into the future with an empty heart.
広場 に は ビル が 建っ て
Buildings rose up in the square,
あの 店 も ない けど レンガ の
and that shop is gone too, but the brick
壁 とか 足元 は そのまま だ ね
walls and ground remain just the same.
ここ に 来れ ば
If I come here,
君 に 会える よ
I can meet you!
「Hey ! ! ruffians ! !
"Hey!! Ruffians!!
kept you waiting , huh ?
Kept you waiting, huh?
can i get a heck yeah ! ?
Can I get a heck yeah!?
let ’s shout “bau” ! !」
Let's shout 'bau'!!"
bau ! ! bau ! ! bau ! ! bau ! !
Bau!! Bau!! Bau!! Bau!!
「Now , hear the howling of my soul ! !
"Now, hear the howling of my soul!!
are you ready ! ?」
Are you ready!?」
「モコちゃん…」
"Moco-chan..."
（bau bau ⬇️ ⬇️）
(Bau bau ⬇️ ⬇️)
ドーナツ リング に 誓っ て
Swearing on the donut ring,
ずっと ずっと 笑顔 を 守る から
I'll protect your smile forever and ever!
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★ 2 匹 が 揃え ば もう 大騒ぎ
Underworld Watchdog Sisters☆★ When the two of us get together, total chaos!
もあ もあ （motto ! !）
Moa moa! (More!!)
ハロハロ （baubau ! !）
Halo halo! (Baubau!!)
迷わ ず に go my way 君 の 絶対 味方 “BAU”DOL です
Without hesitating, go my way! Your absolute ally, the "BAU"DOL!
季節 が いくつ 巡っ て も
No matter how many seasons pass,
どんな に 遠く 離れ て も
no matter how far apart we may be,
忘れない よ キミ の こと を
I'll never forget about you!
夢 見 て いれ ば また 会える
If we keep dreaming, we'll meet again.
ありがとう
Thank you!
FUWAMOCO Birthday Party Night
メン限アンコールライブで待ってるよ～！
See you at our encore live in membership!